-早上好呀 先生们 -早
- Good morning, gentlemen. - Hi.
麦克斯 你睡得好吗
Max, how'd you sleep?
我好喜欢在这儿过夜啊
Oh, I love crashing here!
仿佛回到了大学时代
This is just like college --
熬夜到很晚 昏睡在沙发上
staying up too late, passing out on the couch,
走廊上有毒舌的亚洲女
mean Asian chick down the hall.
是啊 莉莉人呢
Yeah. Where is Lily?
我不知道 去上学了吧
I don't know. S-School, maybe?
我在这儿呢
I'm right here.
我们以前在阿姆斯特丹认识了麦克斯
We met Max in Amsterdam on what we thought
本来是一趟陶艺[大麻]咖啡厅之旅 所以...
was a tour of pottery cafes, so...
很多事我都不记得了
I don't remember much about it,
但我清楚记得
but I do remember thinking
我当时觉得他是我遇过最好笑的人
he was the funniest person I've ever met.
我们跟他说 要是来我们这儿
And we told him if he ever came into town,
必须住咱们家
that he had to stay with us.
他答应了 我真的好开心
And I-I-I'm so glad he said yes
因为我记得当时一直很神经紧张
because I remember being really, uh, paranoid
觉得他不喜欢我
that he didn't like me.
你们俩让开
You two, get out of here.
我来煮早餐给大家吃
I'm gonna whip us up some breakfast.
我的头像兴登堡号一样 痛到炸裂
Whoo! My head feels like the Hindenburg.
少来了
Oh, come on!
-怎么感觉他在欧洲时比较好笑 -对
- I feel like he was funnier in Europe. - Yeah.
米奇尔 快看
Mitchell! Look!
我们巨贵的那瓶红酒吗
Our crazy-expensive bottle of wine?
我们一直想留到最特别的日子才打开的
I -- uh, we were saving this for the perfect occasion.
他一定是等我们睡了 再自己喝掉的
Okay, well, he must've drank it after we went to bed.
谁会这么贱啊
Who does that?
不过问主人家
Just drinks somebody's
就擅自喝掉别人最贵的红酒
most expensive bottle of wine without asking?
-这是仇恨犯罪 -这怎么会是仇恨犯罪
- Okay, it's a hate crime. - How is it a hate crime?
因为我恨他
Because I hate him.
真不敢相信都快被他喝光了
I ca-- I can't believe it's almost gone.
我至今只考虑过打开这瓶酒两次
Look, you know, I've only ever considered opening that twice --
一次是大选之夜刚开始
once early on election night
另一次是我们以为《爱乐之城》得到了最佳影片奖
and then when we thought "La La Land" won Best Picture.
我知道 这一年很不好过
I know. It's been a rough year.
吃早餐啦
Breakfast!
不 不要啊
No, no.
那是我们的鱼子酱吗
Is that our caviar?
是啊 幸好我找到了
Yeah! Lucky I found it.
被藏在冰箱深处呢
It was hiding in the back of the fridge.
因为要留到特别的日子才吃
For a special occasion.
有什么问题吗
Something wrong?
有 有问题
Yeah... yeah.
首先你擅自开了我们价值四百块的红酒
Uh, first you open up our $400 bottle of wine,
现在又开了一罐两百块的鱼子酱
now it's our $200 tin of caviar.
-这都是我们特意留起来的 -留着干嘛
- We were saving those. - For what?
等到庆祝的时候才享用
A celebration, like --
那《月光男孩》得了奥斯卡那次怎么没开
What about when "Moonlight" won the Oscar?
那次对我们群体来说 确实是重要的时刻
Okay, it was a big moment for the community, yes --
这样吧 我还是走吧
Okay, you know what? Look. I'm gonna go, okay?
但听我一句劝 千万别延迟享受人生
But, guys, don't defer enjoyment,
因为人有旦夕祸福
'cause you never know when you're gonna bite it.
要我说 好好享受每一晚
I say, make every night special.
好吧 你这套哲学挺有意思的
Okay, well, that's a -- that's a fun philosophy,
但不是每个人能身体力行 好吗
but not everyone can follow that, okay?
因为我们有责任在身
'Cause -- 'Cause we have responsibilities.
我们有预算
We have -- We have budgets.
我们有个女儿
We have a daughter, you know.
我们女儿人呢
Where is our daughter?
-我不知道 在后院吧 -可能吧
- I don't know. Backyard, maybe? - Maybe.
厄尔·钱伯斯
Earl Chambers,
我昔日的生意搭档 后来变成我的死对头
my former business partner-turned dumbass nemesis,
他买了横向衣柜
bought the old horizontal wardrobe.
给你们衣柜业门外汉解释一下 就是他挂了
For you closet non-pros, that means he died.
然后在上周 我收到了这个骨灰瓮和这封信
Then last week, I received this urn and this note.
"你知道该如何处置我的骨灰
"You know what to do with my ashes.
沿着路一直走"
Follow the path."
这是什么鬼意思
What the hell does that mean?
你以为可以把我逼疯 但你想都别想
You think you can drive me nuts, but you can't.
他听不见你说话的 除非你把盖子打开
He can't actually hear you unless you open the lid.
我还是没想明白
I still can't figure out
"沿着路一直走"是什么意思
the meaning of "Follow the path!"
我要你帮我打给雪儿
I'm gonna need you to call Shirl
搞清楚她爸到底为什么要折磨我
and find out why her father's been torturing me.
-你自己打给她 -你没得选择
- You call her! - That's not an option.
她是个油腻的小滑头 跟她爹一个样
She's a greasy slimebucket, just like her father,
而且不知为何 她不喜欢我
and for some reason, she doesn't like me.
我想想办法吧
Hmm...I'll see what I can do.
曼尼 怎么啦
Hey, Manny! What's up?
你没看到我 一切都很好
I'm not here! Everything's fine!
-超级好 -好吧 我招了
- Super-dupes. - Okay, I'll -- I'll -- I'll talk.
昨晚我和卢克到一片不太安全的社区吃玉米卷
Luke and I went to a sketchy neighborhood for tacos last night,
然后他不见了 之后我再也没看见过他
and he disappeared, and I haven't seen him since.
什么 你最后一次看到他是在哪
What? Where did you see him last?
他跟一个姑娘走了
He went off with this girl.
-跟一个姑娘吗 -是的
- With a girl? - Yeah.
曼尼
Manny.
让我告诉你邓菲家男儿的特质
Let me tell you a little something about Dunphy men.
当我们遇到女性时
When we come into contact with a lady,
总会给她留下炙热灼烧感[性病]
we leave her with a burning sensation.
这么说有点歧义
Let me try that again.
当邓菲男儿遇见性感小妞时
Um...when a Dunphy man sees a sexy skirt,
他就必须"深入"她心房
he's just gotta get in it.
-不妥 -我懂你意思
- No! - I get the point.
我很庆幸你是来跟我说
Look, I'm just glad you came to me...
我才没有 刚好被你逮到而已
I didn't. You caught me here.
因为我不想克莱尔知道后慌张失控
...'cause I don't want Claire freaking out about this.
卢克的电话转到语音信箱了
Luke's phone is going straight to voicemail.
有人在数码门把手上挂了袜子哦
Someone's got a sock on the digital doorknob.
我真的觉得你该担心一下
I really think you should be a little worried about this.
担心
Worried?!
让我告诉你邓菲家男儿的特质
Let me tell you something about Dunphy men.
菲尔 那一区龙蛇混杂 很不安全
Phil, this was a pretty rough neighborhood.
这样吧
Tell you what,
如果能让你放心些
if it makes you feel better,
我们一起去那里找找他
we'll go down there and look around for him.
我们需要支援 强有力的支援
We're gonna need backup -- serious backup.
好了 淡定
Okay, be cool.
我以前就住在这一区
I used to live in this neighborhood.
只要表现得强悍 就没人敢惹你
If you act tough, nobody will mess with you.
你们想尝尝
Would you like to try
人道的碱水刨冰吗
a cruelty-free alkaline-water snow cone?
-什么 -免费品尝
- What? - Free sample.
去我们的店里有大份的
You can get a larger one down at our stand.
我们还提供翻修乐器大号的服务
We also refurbish tubas.
不用 谢谢
No, thank you.
我的街区怎么了
What happened to my neighborhood?
祝你们今天愉快
Have the best day.
留络腮胡的白人毁了一切
White people with beards -- they ruined everything.
你为什么要说这里危险
Why would you even say that this place was dangerous?
晚上这里可怕多了 还放着爵士乐呢
It was a lot scarier at dark. There was jazz.
卢克还是不接电话
Luke's still not answering.
我们会找到他的 菲尔
We're gonna find him, Phil.
我不担心 我经历过
Oh, I-I'm not worried. I've been there.
遇见一个女孩 忘了地点和时间
Meet a girl, you lose track of place and time,
不仅是因为你的罗盘表不见了
not just 'cause your compass watch is missing,
结果她表哥罗德尼突然也有了同一块表
and suddenly her cousin Rodney has the exact same watch
他还发誓他有那表很久了
but swears it was always his.
瞧瞧 马里奥的汽修店
Oh, look! Mario's Bodyshop.
至少有一样东西还没变
At least one thing is still the same.
这条街上发生的一切
There's nothing that happens in this street
地头蛇马里奥全都了如指掌
that Mario doesn't know about.
我们过去吧
Let's go over there.
红灯闪烁 警报响个不停
So, red lights are flashing, alarms are blaring.
还有大概十秒钟反应堆就要熔毁了 温度高到
We're about 10 seconds from a meltdown so hot
会将比利时烧成一汪热巧克力
it's gonna turn Belgium into a pool of hot chocolate.
我突然意识到
And I suddenly realize,
他们没有正确地计算相对扭曲...
they haven't properly accounted for the relativistic distort--
这栋楼是几号楼
Hey, what's this building's number?
我想叫杯思慕雪外送
I'm trying to Postmates a smoothie.
我迅速在脑海中进行了
I quickly do a few multi-dimensional
一些多维张量计算
tensor calculations in my head,
我将吓哭的警卫推到一边
I push this crying guard to one side
调整了同步加速器
and adjust the synchrotron.
我抬头看着倒计时钟
I look up at the countdown clock.
你 拿着电话的
You, with the phone!
-你叫什么 -艾丽克斯·邓菲
- What's your name? - Alex Dunphy.
邓菲女士 我拯救世界
Ms. Dunphy, is my story of saving the world
同时意外创造三种新元素的故事让你觉得无聊吗
whilst accidently creating three new elements boring you?
没有 没有 完全没有
Uh, no. No, no, no, no, no.
很抱歉 教授
I'm so sorry, Professor.
你说的话永远不会让我觉得无聊
Nothing you could say would ever bore me.
我尊敬你
I revere you.
实际上 去年万圣节我扮成了你
I actually went as you last year for Halloween.
好吧 这是我的手机 别怪我妹妹
Okay, it's my phone. Don't blame my sister.
切尔西 回头再给你回电话
Hey, Chelsea. Gonna have to call you back.
-我不信 你闭嘴 -闭嘴
- Shut up! Shut up! - Shut up!
不好意思 切尔西的朋友
Excuse me, Chelsea's friend.
你看起来不像是我的学生
Y-You don't look like one of my students.
谢谢 你嘴真甜
Oh, thank you! That is so sweet.
不是 你为什么来这里
No. Why are you here?
我今天有个重要的工作面试
Oh, I have a really big job interview today,
我需要有人检查下我写的...
and I need someone to look over what I wrote for my --
我们走了 我带她出去 很抱歉
Yeah, we're going. I'm taking her out. I am so sorry.
干嘛 是他问的 你太没礼貌了
What? He asked. You're being rude.
-太暴露了 -出去
- Very revealing. - Get out.
克莱尔 很高兴你给我打了电话
Claire, I'm so glad you called.
我们之前怎么从来没聚过
How come we've never done this before?
因为我们两家是世仇
Because we were born into a feud.
血仇世家哈特菲尔德和麦科伊 鲨鱼队和喷气机队
Hatfields and McCoys, the Sharks and Jets,
衣柜疯子和衣柜笨蛋
the -- the closet lunatic and the closet idiot.
-顺便说一句 很遗憾你爸爸去世了 -谢谢
- By the way, I'm really sorry about your dad. - Thanks.
你知道他为什么让人把骨灰寄给我爸爸吗
Do you have any idea why he had his ashes sent to my dad?
-也许是为了把他逼疯吧 -效果拔群
- Probably to drive him bonkers. - Well, it's working.
他知道了会很高兴的
That would've made him happy.
咱们约定吧 永远不要像他们一样
Let's make a pact -- to never be like them.
我同意
I am in.
我们是男性统治行业中的两个女人
We are two women in a male-dominated industry.
我们该帮助彼此
We should help each other.
实际上 你知道有谁会做
Actually, do you have any sources
古董菠萝把手吗
for antique pineapple knobs?
我们在做殖民地系列
We're doing this whole colonial line --
拉兹罗肯定知道
Ooh, I bet you Lazlo would know.
他是我们的首席设计师
He's our lead designer.
大家都知道拉兹罗是谁 他是个传奇
Everybody knows who Lazlo is. He's a legend.
也是我唯一一个有价值的员工
Yeah, and my only employee worth a damn.
机器人工人 那才是未来
Robot workers. Now, that's the future.
对啊 它们从不休息
Right! They work 24/7,
而且你不用给它们买生日蛋糕
and you don't have to buy them a birthday cake.
机器人变得更像人类时
Yeah, and as they become more human,
你就可以说 你 来我办公室
you can be like, "Hey, you, come into my office",
-然后"吃干抹净"了它们 -是啊
- and then you just go to town on them. - Yeah.
什么鬼
What the hell?
汽修店怎么了
What happened to the bodyshop?
我们只是保留了招牌
Oh, we just kept the sign.
马里奥不在了吗
Oh, uh, so -- so no M-Mario?
是啊 我们是艺术家联盟
Mnh-mnh. We're an artist collective.
吉莉安玩毛线艺术
Jillian works in yarn,
芒福德用乐高做雕像 邓肯是画家
Mumford sculpts with Lego, Duncan is a painter.
我能给你们写首诗吗
May I write you a poem?
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
我就跟你说有这职业
I told you it was a career.
你有没有见过我儿子
Um, any chance that you have, uh, seen my son?
没有 抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
好吧 他昨晚来了这附近
Oh, okay. He -- He was around here last night.
他貌似跟这附近的一个姑娘走了
He apparently went off with a girl from this neighborhood.
从那以后我们再也没能联系上他
We just haven't been able to reach him since.
你知道那姑娘的名字吗
Do you know the girl's name?
不知道 像是个拉丁名字
No. Uh, something Latin-y.
你怎么了 你以前还是拉丁男孩呢
What happened to you? You used to be Latin-y.
能描述一下她的外貌吗
Can you describe her?
棕色头发 高颧骨
Brown hair, high cheekbones --
他要做什么 用乐高把她做出来吗
What is he gonna do, build her out of Legos?
万万没想到会有如此神效
Huh, that is surprisingly effective.
等等 我认识那姑娘
Wait a minute. I know that girl.
她好像在一家小蛋糕店工作
I think she works at a cupcake shop.
真棒 在哪里
Great. Where is it?
我不确定是哪家 因为这里有四家
Well, I'm not sure which one because we have four.
一家叫"小蛋糕!" 加了个感叹号
There's Cupcakes! With an exclamation point,
卖素食小蛋糕的"小淡糕"
there's vegan cupcakes at Cupfakes,
"狗蛋糕"是买给狗狗的宠物小蛋糕店
there's Pupcakes, which sells cupcakes for dogs,
还有"瑞克的录像机修理店"
and then there's Rick's VCR Repair.
那家的小蛋糕最好吃
Oh, they make the best cupcakes.
白痴麦克斯 害我们得在
Stupid Max, forcing us to eat our caviar
在如此普通的周五早上吃鱼子酱
on a regular Friday morning.
我根本无法享受鱼子酱的美味
I can't even enjoy the symphony of flavors,
或它在我口中融化的感觉
or the -- or the way that it melts in my mouth.
那你干嘛不随便喝口剩下的酒咽下去得了
Why don't you just wash it down with whatever wine's left.
对呀 干嘛不呢
Yeah, why don't I.
-干杯 -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
果然不出所料 你知道吗
Mmm, and, of course, you know what?
这俩绝配
It pairs perfectly.
我不敢相信我吃着一生最棒的一顿饭
I-I cannot believe I'm having one of the best meals of my life
却没有庆祝任何事情
and we're not even celebrating anything.
谢谢了 麦克斯
Yeah, thanks, Max!
-谢谢了麦克斯 -谢你全家啊麦克斯
- Thank you, Max. - Thank you, Max.
小卡 有没有可能
Cam, is it -- is it -- is it possible
我们其实真的很享受
that we're actually enjoying ourselves
麦克斯是对的
and -- and that Max was right?
或许我们真的总在延迟享受
Maybe we do defer enjoyment.
那些没用完的飞行里程
All those unspent frequent flyer miles,
那我等了好久才穿的靴子
the boots that I have waited so long to wear
穿时已经过时了
that they're no longer in style,
还有那些冲浪板
the -- the -- the surfboards
咱们从来没用过
that we've never used because
因为要等到最完美的冲浪日子
it just "had to be the perfect beach day".
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
-米奇尔 -我要点了它
- Mitchell... - I'm lighting it.
-不 -我要点了它
-No! - I'm lighting it!
不 这是印有名字的婚礼蜡烛
No, that is our monogrammed wedding candle,
我们要把它留到特殊场合
and we're supposed to save it.
什么场合呢 小卡
For what, Cam?
-我不知道 -你不知道
- I don't know! - You don't know.
- I don't. - You don't know.
看
Ohh...look at it.
好像闻到了永恒的爱
Smells like eternal love.
好吧
Aww...oh. O-kay.
为什么你老在我办公室
Why are you always in my office?
我在这儿效率最高
I do my best work in here.
我在试着进入他的思路
I've been trying to get into his head.
我甚至还买了他最喜欢的午饭
I even brought his favorite lunch --
鸡尾酒虾 波本酒
shrimp cocktail and bourbon.
那不过是你每天午餐吃的东西啊
Or that's just what you have for lunch every day.
这也是厄尔从我那里偷学走的
That's another thing Earl stole from me!
-你发现什么了 -首先
- What did you find out? - First of all,
雪儿不知道有关骨灰的任何事
Shirl doesn't know anything about the ashes.
其次 我们不会
And second, we're not
像你俩一样不和
gonna be a part of your little feud anymore.
-我们会成为朋友 -她耍你呢
- We're gonna be friends. - She's playing you!
-不会 -我问你
- No... -Let me ask you a question.
你告诉她我们投标贝尔蒙特花园了吗
Did you tell her we're bidding on Belmont Gardens?
没 怎么了
No. Why?
因为15分钟前 我接到个电话
Because 15 minutes ago, I got a phone call
说突然之间
saying just out of the blue,
"衣柜衣柜衣柜衣柜"公司和我们竞标
Closets Closets Closets Closets is bidding against us.
她看了你的提案了吗
Did she see your proposal?
看了 爸 我肯定
Yes, Dad! I'm quite sure she
她在我去卫生间的时候翻了我的包
rifled through my bag when I was in the bathroom.
你去卫生间了吗
You went to the bathroom?
-你咋不直接把公司送她呢 -天啊
- Why don't you just give her the company?! - Oh, God.
-你瞧 番茄酱 -这说明什么
- Bingo! Ketchup! - What does that prove?
她午餐是不是吃了番茄酱
Did she have ketchup for lunch?
她的确吃了薯条
She had... French fries.
证据确凿
There's your smoking gun.
玛格丽特 我需要
Margaret? I'm gonna need
薯条和番茄酱来进入雪儿的思路
fries and ketchup to get in Shirl's head.
不不 雪儿不会这么做的
No! No, Shirl wouldn't have done this.
坏消息
Um, bad news.
我们好不容易找到的那些菠萝把手
Uh, we finally tracked down those pineapple knobs,
但刚被买下 是衣柜
but they were all just bought up by Closets...
-不 -衣柜
- No. - Closets...
不 玛格丽特
No, Margaret!
衣柜衣柜公司
...Closets Closets.
雪儿玩了我
Shirl screwed me.
你知道你要怎么做吗
You know what you have to do?
你得戳她的痛处
You've got to hit her where it hurts.
她最珍视什么
What does she value most?
拉兹罗
Lazlo.
我觉得你没明白
I don't think you understand
这对我来说有多丢人
how humiliating that was for me.
这尴尬可能会缠着我一辈子
There are parts of me that will never uncringe.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我打断了无聊的故事而已
So I interrupted some boring story.
阿尔文·费诺曼博士
Dr. Arvin Fennerman
是一个大奖的两次获得者
is a two-time Vanderkoff Grant winner --
一次是哲学一次是几何学
one for philosophy and one for geometry.
你不能就这么...
You can't put him into a box
-因为 -你能不能看下我的文章
- because... - Could you please just read my sample?
这个工作对我来说很重要
This job is important to me.
这是我有一份真正工作的唯一机会
This is my one shot at a real career.
好 我读 但"真正工作"吗
Fine, I'll read it. And "Real career"?
我看过这个诺普公司的吧
I've seen this NERP business.
妮可·罗丝玛丽·佩奇看起来就有病
Nicole Rosemary Page seems bonkers.
她不是因为食人事件出事了吗
Didn't she get in trouble for cannibalism?
没有 事实证明没有法律禁止
No. Turns out there are no laws against
吃自己的阑尾
eating your own appendix,
而且这样有助于保持身材
and it does help with fine lines.
但她是个成功的典范
But she's a success story.
童星 邦德女郎
Child star, bond girl,
在钱全被方氏骗局卷走前还是独立甜心
indie darling before she lost all her money to a Fonzie scheme.
-你说的是庞氏骗局吧 -很遗憾 还真不是呢
- Don't you mean Ponzi scheme? - Sadly, no.
然后出于绝望 她成立了诺普
So, out of desperation, she invented NERP,
接下来突然之间就成为商业帝国
and next thing you know -- boom! Empire.
我只想成为伟大事业的一部分
I just want to be a part of something great.
说实话
Well, if I'm being honest,
你写得还不错
your writing sample's actually pretty good.
真的吗 谢谢
Really?! Thank you.
天啊 费诺曼博士
Oh, my God. It's Dr. Fennerman.
别思考 别呼吸 头低下
Don't think, don't breathe, keep your head down. O-kay.
你们好
Hello.
不好意思 你好 博士
Sorry! Hello, Doctor.
要下坐吗
Would you like down sit?
-什么鬼 -太好了你人 艾丽克斯
- What? - Kind, that's very you of, Alex.
再和我说下 你为什么在我的班上
Um...tell me again, why were you in my class?
我有个很重要的面试
I have a very big interview
是和妮可·罗丝玛丽·佩奇 她刚刚...
with Nicole Rosemary Page, and she was just --
你知道她是个江湖骗子吧
Ugh! You know she's a snake oil salesman, right?
我知道
Yes, I know.
人们一直抱怨腹泻
People complain about the diarrhea all the time,
但减肥不就...
but that is the point.
她的科学就是一派胡言
Her science is utter nonsense.
什么能给你能量的宇宙贴纸
I mean, space stickers that give you energy,
能吸收无线网信号的水晶
and crystals that absorb Wi-Fi,
1200块一双的袜子 有没有搞错
and seriously -- $1,200 socks?
做袜子的羊毛出自只吃寿司的羊
Those sheep eat nothing but sushi.
-我们说完没有 -神奇的是 没有
- Are we done here? - Surprisingly, not.
这或许听起来很疯狂 但
This might sound crazy, but...
我要和你结婚
I'm going to marry you.
什么
What?!
抱歉 你第一次和活生生的女生说话吗
I'm sorry, first time talking to a real girl?
不 听我说 我也搞不懂
No, l-l-listen. I-I-I don't get it.
其实我也吓到了
Frankly, it boggles the mind,
但自从刚才遇见你
but I've been running
我在脑袋里运算了数十种可能的情形
dozens of probability scenarios in my head since we met,
最终结果都是我们
and-and they all end with us...
在一起了
...together.
我这辈子也听过不少很瞎的搭讪词 但...
I have heard some lame pickup lines in my day, but --
那种词我也有不少存货
I have plenty of those.
你是神经电流吗
Are you a neuro-electrical current
因为你整天都在我脑袋里跑来跑去
because you've been running through my mind all day?
但这次不一样
But th-th-that's not what this is.
咱俩肯定会在一起 海莉·邓菲
This is going to happen, Haley Dunphy.
-你怎么知道我的名字 -我什么都知道
- Ew, how do you know my name? - I know everything.
而且你的通行证上面有名字
Also, your pass has your name written on it.
我觉得我要晕过去了
I think I'm gonna pass out.
我把我的联系方式空投到你电话上了
Right, I've just air-dropped my contact info to your phone.
要不你就按一下接受
You just tap to accept it.
我是不会"要"的
Uh, yeah, not gonna...tap that.
我认为你会的
I think you will.
海莉 宇宙中有许多力
Haley, there are forces in the universe
是我们无法理解的
that we don't understand...
可测却无法解释的力
measurable forces that...can't be explained,
但没人能否认它的存在
but cannot be denied...
咱俩之间就是这样
and that's-that's what this is.
我也无法理解 但我知道它是真实存在的
I don't get it, but...I know that it's real.
这也太智障了吧
That was so dumb!
什么 哪里智障 你才智障
What? No, it wasn't. You're-you're dumb.
会烙印进你脑海的 我已在你脑海之中
That's gonna stick. I'm-I'm in your head.
-好吧 -等着瞧
- Okay. - You'll see.
行行行 兄弟 走人时尽量走得帅一点
Sure, buddy. Now try and walk away cool.
-我会的 -那好
- Oh, I will. - Okay.
我们本来在这里亲热
We were standing right here making out.
突然间他说"我去去就回"
All of a sudden, he said, "I'll be right back",
之后我就没见过他了
and that was the last I saw of him.
各位 我的休息时间结束了
You guys, my break is over,
我希望你们能找到他
but I hope you find him.
谢谢你的帮助
Thank you for your help,
顺带一提 小蛋糕很好吃
and the cupcakes are delicious, by the way.
-那是给狗狗吃的 -不是吧
- Those are for dogs. - Oh, no.
-菲尔 你没事吧 -没事没事
- Ay, Phil, are you okay? - Yeah, yeah.
我很肯定卢克是有什么充分的理由
I'm sure there's a perfectly reasonable explanation
才会放弃和女孩亲热
why Luke would abandon a make-out sesh.
不 根本没有
No, there isn't.
邓菲家的男人永远不会那样做
A Dunphy man would never do that.
我们会临阵脱逃 被蜘蛛吓跑
We walk away from fights, we walk away from spiders,
但永远不会离开身上有糖霜味的可爱女孩
but never a super-cute girl who smells like frosting!
你得保持乐观
You have to stay positive.
高级家具店的附近从来不会出什么事
Nothing bad ever happens this close to a Pottery Barn.
我一直在假装勇敢
I've been putting on a brave face
来压制内心的黑暗
to squash the darkness inside of me,
但万一发生了最坏的状况呢
but what if the worst has happened?
我该怎么和克莱尔说 我不说
How will I tell Claire? I won't.
我得用枕头捂死她免得她伤心
I'll have to smother her with a pillow to spare her the pain,
但那样杰就会失去女儿
but then Jay will have lost a daughter.
我得把他也捂死
I'll have to smother him, too.
那两只枕头是成套的 成了我的惯用手法
That's two pillows from the same set. It's a pattern.
-我被警察盯上了 -给老娘打起精神来
- The police are after me! - Get ahold of yourself!
你手也太重了
What the hell?
不是我 你瞧 我手还没落下去呢
It wasn't me. Look, I'm still cocked!
是只鞋
It was a shoe.
等等 这是
Wait, that's...
是卢克的鞋
that's Luke's.
卢克 你没事
Luke! You're okay!
我被困在屋顶上了
I got stuck on the roof.
这下我放心了
I'm so relieved!
我不用捂死你妈了
I don't have to kill your mother!
原来卢克当时要上厕所
Turns out, Luke had to go to the bathroom.
有人告诉他厕所在楼上
Someone told him it was upstairs,
他就一路上到了屋顶
so he walked all the way up to the roof
不小心把自己反锁在屋顶了
and locked himself out.
他电话没电了 街上音乐声太大
His phone was dead, and he-he lost his voice
他大声喊得嗓子也哑了
trying to scream over the street musicians.
我松了口气 跑上去狠狠亲了他一口
I was so relieved, I ran up there and gave him a big kiss.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria!
我们被困住了
Hi. We're stuck.
你上来帮我们开个门行吗
Could you pop on up and open the door?
邓菲家男儿啊
Dunphy men.
你好 拉兹萝
Hello, Lazlo.
-发音是"拉兹罗" -我就是这么念的啊
- It's pronounced "Lazlo". - That's what I said.
谢谢你来见我们
Thank you so much for meeting with us.
你有没有考虑我们的提议
Have you had a chance to consider our offer
加入普利切特衣柜
to join Pritchett's Closets?
我有兴趣 但我有张条件单
I'm intrigued, but I have a list of demands.
好的 当然
Ah, yes, of course.
条件有
We have, uh...
"两个装满白色口香糖的绿松石碗
...uh, "Two turquoise bowls of white Chiclets,
有地漏的空办公室"
an empty office with a drain in the floor..."
-"尖叫室"是什么 -这还用解释吗
- What's a "Scream room"? - I think that's self-explanatory.
普里契特
Pritchett!
厄尔闺女
Girl Earl!
你居然想从我这挖走拉兹罗
You're actually trying to poach Lazlo from me?
我还以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
本来是 可你买走了所有菠萝门把手
We were, and then you bought all my pineapple knobs.
-买来送你的 -什么
- As a gift! - What?
-我发到你那去了 -是吗
- I had them sent to you. - You did?
别被她蛊惑
Don't listen to her.
这都是她变态计划的一部分
This is all part of some sick plan.
偷看克莱尔的提案
Stealing Claire's proposals,
送来厄尔的骨灰让我闹心
Earl's urn to get in my head.
但你的小伎俩是不会成功的
But your little games are not gonna work.
是的 你要怎么解释
Yeah. Yeah, how do you explain
我提案上面的番茄酱 薯条妹
the red ketchup stains on my proposal, French Fries?
我从不沾番茄酱
I never use ketchup.
我吃薯条跟与拉兹罗亲密时一样
I like my fries the way I like my Lazlo...
光着来
undressed.
小低低
Twiddle-Dee.
你们俩的关系好复杂啊
You guys have a really complicated relationship.
你那红色的污渍是什么
And what's that red stain?
鸡尾酒虾酱
Shrimp cocktail sauce, uh-oh.
爸
Dad!
-雪儿 -省省吧
- Shirl... - Save it.
我们本来可以当好朋友呢 但算了吧
We could have been friends. Well, forget it.
要战便战
Game on.
雪儿
Shirl...
她有什么诡计
What is she up to?
没有 你的神经病阴谋论害我损失了朋友
No, no. Your crazy conspiracy theories just cost me a friend.
我还以为我终于找到了
I thought I'd finally found
一个业界盟友
an -- an ally in this industry,
一个与我... 共登山巅的伙伴
somebody to... to climb the hill with.
共登山巅 天啊 就是这个
Up the hill! Oh, my God! That's it!
不行 不许你现在跟我来顿悟这招
No, no, you do not get to have an epiphany right now!
我要被你气炸了
I am furious at you!
我的回答是 我愿意
The answer is...yes.
很多人说诺普
People say that NERP
不过是骗钱的玩意
is nothing more than a con job,
脑残女演员的刷脸骗钱项目
a cash-grab vanity project from a kooky actress.
抱歉 这是在提问吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Was that a question?
-不是 -那就好
- No. - Oh, okay.
但是
But...
真是这样吗
is it true?
-他们总不跟我说真话 -"他们"是指谁
- They don't tell me things. - Who's "They"?
但我不觉得诺普是个生意
See, I don't see NERP as, like, a business.
-这更像是种... -生活方式 我也是
- It's more, like, a kind of... - Like a way of life! Me too!
迪士尼创办人华特·迪士尼曾发想过
Walt Disney once... envisioned...
一个魔法世界...
a magical world...
但别人都说他是疯子
...and people told him he was mad.
他们称那地方为"华特蠢地"
They called it "Walt's Folly."
-但你知道后来那里变成哪儿了吗 -迪士尼乐园
- But you know what that place became? - Disneyland.
-我没有在问你 -对不起
- That was not a question. - Oh, I -- I'm sorry.
那地方成了迪士尼乐园
That place is Disneyland.
真的假的 不是吧 完全没猜到
What?! That's crazy. Didn't see it coming.
我希望把我公司
I want to turn NERP
变成下一个迪士尼 脸书 特斯拉 肉毒针
into the next Disney-Facebook-Tesla-Botox.
能改变世界 变成通向未来的道路
It's a world changer. It's a road map to the future.
这是个问题啊
That was a question!
算了 听我说
Alright, listen.
我很喜欢你写的样品文章 真心的
I really liked your writing sample, it's true.
但是...
But...
我们有很多应征者
...we have a lot of candidates
有丰富的经验 更有名气的父母
with more experience and famous-er parents,
所以...
so...
飞走吧 小鸟
fly away, little birdie.
啪嗒 啪嗒 啪嗒
Flap. Flap, flap.
好吧 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
妮可
Nicole?
你和我 咱俩肯定能行
You and me -- this is gonna happen.
你说什么
Excuse me?
宇宙中有许多力是我们无法理解的
There are forces in the universe that we don't understand.
它们无法被解释 但它们的存在也无法否认
They can't be explained, but they cannot be denied,
而我们也是一样
and that is what this is.
我无法理解 但我知道这是真实存在的
I don't -- I don't get it, but I know that it's real.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我也是这么跟那些喷子说的
That is just what I said to all of those haters
就是那些说我的水晶能量贴纸
who told me that my crystal energy stickers
并不能改善结肠健康的人
did not improve your colon health.
神经病
Uh! Crazy.
是能有效的 只要...
They do if you, you know...
是啊
Yeah.
所以下周一早上我们能再见吗
So, um, does that mean that I will see you Monday morning?
周二吧
Let's make it Tuesday
因为我周一喜欢在漂浮缸里待着
'cause I like to spend Mondays in a flotation tank.
年轻时 我们沿着这条路爬到这棵老橡树
As young men, we'd hike this path up to an old oak tree,
我们一起动脑想着怎么征服衣柜世界
where we'd brainstorm how to conquer the closet universe.
我们当年傻傻地以为自己什么都懂
We foolishly thought that we knew everything back then.
但我乐观地希望我这些年来有学到几件事
But hopefully, I've learned a few things through the years.
比如 仿佛没有明天般认真活在当下
Like, live today as if there is no tomorrow.
弥补过去的错误何时都不晚
it's not too late to right past wrongs,
当一切都在走下坡时 要向上看
and when things are looking down, look up...
抓住你永远以为自己不会尝试的机会
...or take chances you never imagined you would.
"你个傻逼娘炮 我就知道你会做
"You stupid softy, I knew you'd do it.
你有没有有试着搞点煽情的啊
Did you try to do something special?
是不是日落时分
Was it at sunset?
就是日落时分 对吧
It was at sunset, wasn't it?
娘们 我赢了
Sucker. I win.
咱们地狱再见"
See you in hell."
我拭目以待
I look forward to that.
这太爽了
Whoo! Ohh, this is amazing!
对啊 我们好几年前就该这么做了
I know! We should have done this years ago.
我有点冷啊 你是不是也有点冷
Whoa. I'm a little cold. Are you a little cold?
是啊 我还没被冻僵的部位的确有点冷
Yeah, the parts of me that I can still feel sure are. Yeah.
看看那些下班在回家路上的废柴
Oh, look at those suckers on their way home from work.
祝生意场狗咬狗愉快啊
Enjoy the rat race!
-别忘了要纳税啊 -对啊
- Don't forget to pay your taxes! - Yeah!
你有没有读到那个... 恐龙鱼的文章
Hey, did you see the story about that, um, dinosaur fish?
文章说它的头... 是个蛇的头之类的
It said it had the head of... a head of a snake or something.
有 有16排牙齿嘛
Yeah, 16 rows of teeth, uh-huh.
你觉得我们从水下看像两只海豹吗
Hey, do you think that we look like seals from underneath?
米奇尔 我们这是在干嘛
Mitchell, w-what are we doing?
我们在干... 我们这是在享受人生啊
What are we... We're living our lives, is what we're doing.
是啊 我知道 我只是问问
Yeah, but I, uh, I'm just asking,
但想象是不是比现实做更有意思啊
but was imagining it more fun?
好歹更暖和
Well, it was warmer.
你知道吗 我很喜欢期待一件事情
You know, I like looking forward to things.
女歌手卡莉·赛门的名曲是"预期"
Carly Simon's big hit was "Anticipation",
不是"还记得我们做过的那些牛逼事"吗
not "Remember That Cool Thing We Did".
我有个主意
Hey, I have an idea.
我们就回去 买一瓶永远没机会开的酒
L-Let's go back, we'll buy a bottle of wine that we'll never open
一根永远没机会点的蜡烛
and a candle that we'll never light,
-然后今天就收工 -这主意听起来很赞
- call it a day, huh? - That sounds wonderful.
好了 但你别再碰我脚了
Okay, but stop touching my feet.
我没碰你脚
I didn't touch you.
我没碰你的脚
-你没... -我没碰你
- You didn't... - I didn't touch you.
-恐龙鱼 是恐龙鱼 -恐龙鱼 恐龙鱼
- Dinosaur fish! Dinosaur fish! - Dinosaur fish! Dinosaur fish!
米奇尔 米奇尔 不许你留下我一个人
Mitchell! Mitchell, do not leave me alone!